Oh!
(Leonard:)Look, do I think
that you are talented
(Leonard:)and that you are beautiful?
Of course I do.
(Leonard:)But isn't Los Angeles
full of actresses
(Leonard:)who are just as talented,
just as beautiful?
(Leonard:)Look, we'll come back to that.
(Penny:)No, please. Don't stop, go on.
(Penny:)Tell me how I'm gonna be a waitress
for the rest of my life.
(Leonard:)That is not what I said.
Look, I think you're really good.
(Leonard:)I truly do.
(Leonard:)But this is an incredibly hard thing
that you're shooting for.
(Leonard:)I mean, the odds of anyone
becoming a successful actor
(Leonard:)-are like a million to one.
-Wow, thank you.
(Leonard:)Should've let Sheldon come.
(Sheldon:)This is interesting.
(Sheldon:)Apparently, a key component
in some forms of humor
(Sheldon:)-is the element of surprise.
-Well, that makes sense.